ARJUN SAJI

Scarborough, ON

+14376621536

arjun000saji@gmail.com

I am a passionate and hardworking employee with experience working in busy kitchens. I have proven myself as a valuable team member, quickly learning many stations in a short period of time. I possess good communication skills and maintain a positive attitude towards my coworkers.

Work experience

Earls Kitchen + bar King West(November 2023)

Line cook- I have worked in Dishwashing, Appetizers and Sushi, Salads, and Pan fry.

Amazon office staff (September 2022- June 2023)

Sorting

Inbound check

Outbound check

Route assigning

Cashier (June2022- August 2022)

Greeted customers upon their entry into the store and helped them with any questions and concerns.

Opened store on 30% of shifts, including opening cash drawer and front door and fulfilling 30-point opening checklist.

Collaborated with 20 team members to hit 90% + customer satisfaction. Closed store 2 days per week, including delivery of cash bag to the bank

Education

SMV HSS, Poonjar (INDIA)

High school diploma- Computer Science (2020- 2022)

Centennial College, Progress Campus, Scarborough (Canada)

Software Engineering Technology (AI)

Skills

Computer skills

Communication skills

Managerial

Time management